Hi everyone, my name is Harita. This is the sample test case, a voice recording for to check auto caption generator.
And I just want to write some, sorry, say some information.
I was doing this auto caption generator by using the python and by using some libraries called different libraries.
We are having just need to import that file. Let me explain that what are those files.
In this we just need to import first one, import viscure and srt and date and time and oes and systems.
We just need to import these things and next we need to go for the further method or functions.
Writing that, matching the path name, file name is it okay or not.
Which will generate a file not for error or error loading viscure model or as file not for error during transcription.
Any other things, but if it successfully completed means it will generate the text as subtitled saved as output with the information captions.satty.
It is saved in the format of asatty file. So let me check that it will generate the text or not.